ILGWU 4x5 Negatives of Photographs 5780 P N45
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series Local 105
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 172)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 173)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 174)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 175)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 176)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 177)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 178)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 179)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 180)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 181)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 182)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 183)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 184)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 185)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 186)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 187)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 188)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 189)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 190)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 191)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 192)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 193)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 194)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 195)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 196)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 197)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 198)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 199)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 200)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 201)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 202)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 203)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 204)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 205)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 206)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 207)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 208)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 209)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 210)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 211)
- Series Local 117
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 212)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 213)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 214)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 215)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 216)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 217)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 218)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 219)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 220)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 221)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 222)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 223)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 224)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 225)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 226)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 227)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 228)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 229)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 230)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 231)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 232)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 233)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 234)
  - Unknown (Box 33, Folder 235)
- Series Local 121
  - Agreement Manager Nicholas Kirtzman (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Series Local 124
  - Louis Quintilliano (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Celebration of 35 hour work week with Stulberg, Kreindler and Louis Quintiliano (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Series Local 132
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Retirement for Feldman at Commodore Hotel, 2/21/59, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Installation by Louis Nelson Vice President, 2/26/53, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Contract signing Servazipper Corporation 36 30 on Lawrence Street Flushing New York, 1/20/53, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - 20th Anniversary Celebration Hotel Commodore, 3/9/57, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Installed as Manager, 2/59, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - New manager at work Joel Menist, 1/22/59, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Series Local 135
  - Newark Unity Weekend, 9/9/35, 1935 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Series Local 138
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Society help (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Strike picket line (Box 34, Folder 21)
- Series Local 142
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Central Needle Trades High School 225 West 24th 25th Anniversary District Attorney Hogan, Goodell, Stulberg and Joe Tuvim, 10/27/58, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Stoppage new agreement vote at Hotel Diplomat, 3/5/59, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Retirees meet monthly at Headquarters, executive members vote to support Forum Bill, 9/23/59, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Presentation of oil portrait to George and Mrs. Meany, 12/6/57, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Installation by Louis Stulberg Central Needle High School, 3/15/56, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - Council sign contract, 8/10/54, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - Daniel Salk and Joseph Tuvim, 3/3/54, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 42)
  - Central Needle High School 20th Anniversary, 10/22/53, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 43)
  - Louigi Antonini speaking at Installation, 3/9/53, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 44)
  - Unity House, 6/59, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 45)
  - Book 29th Anniversary Groups and Industrial, 9/22/52, 1952 (Box 34, Folder 46)
  - Boxer (Box 34, Folder 47)
  - Unity Weekend, 6/29/51, 1951 (Box 34, Folder 48)
  - Impartial Chairman Installation Nathan Wolf, 2/15/50, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 49)
  - Stoppage Webster Hall, 10/49, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 50)
  - Shoulder Pad association Herman Laudow Trea., Jack Ulrich Executive Director, Nathan Wolf Impartial Chair, Joseph Tuvim and Ann Bruno Weiss Committee 142, 12/4/51, 1951 (Box 34, Folder 51)
  - Installation, 3/9/53, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 52)
  - 19th Anniversary Central Trades High School W 24th Street between 7th and 8th Avenue A. Harriman, Franklin D. Roosevelt Jr., Mintzer and Dubinsky, 10/29/52, 1952 (Box 34, Folder 53)
  - Installation meeting, 3/9/53, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 54)
  - Joe Tuvim and Mrs. Betsie Tonino chief of Womens Worker section discuss homework (Box 34, Folder 55)
  - 16th Anniversary at Old Romanian Restaurant, 10/25/49, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 56)
  - Joe Tuvim, Bell Burker chair and Executive Board Member Christmas Party at Old Romanian Restaurant, 12/18/52, 1952 (Box 34, Folder 57)
  - Left to Right Tuvim, Harry C. Oppenheimer textile, Glen Adams WFDR Communications, Elmer A. Carter discuss Care of Jonny Wilson, 7/19/50 (Box 34, Folder 58)
  - Pioneer Women of 142 honor Tuvim with scroll, 10/2/50, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 59)
  - Joe Tuvim (Box 34, Folder 60)
  - Joe Tuvim (Box 34, Folder 61)
- Series Local 155
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 62)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 63)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 64)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 65)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 66)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 67)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 68)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 69)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 70)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 71)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 72)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 73)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 74)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 75)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 76)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 77)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 78)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 79)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 80)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 81)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 82)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 83)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 84)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 85)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 86)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 87)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 88)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 89)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 90)
  - Red Cross Certificate (Box 34, Folder 91)
  - Ratification (Box 34, Folder 92)
  - Nelson Louis (Box 34, Folder 93)
  - Education in Shop Gus Tyler speaks to 100 workers at Laurel Knitting Mills (Box 34, Folder 94)
  - Local 102 Blood Bank, 4/15/50, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 95)
  - Local 102 Member meet for new contract and Red Cross Blood Bank for Korea, 12/10/50, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 96)
  - Local 102 Executive Board For Journal, 1/17/53, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 97)
  - Local 102 Birthday party for member (Box 34, Folder 98)
  - Local 102 Shop Chairman meet (Box 34, Folder 99)
  - Local 102 Committee (Box 34, Folder 100)
  - Local 102 Credit Union and Conference (Box 34, Folder 101)
  - Local 102 Retirement of members (Box 34, Folder 102)
  - Local 102 Membership meet hear new contract terms (Box 34, Folder 103)
  - Local 102 Christmas party show (Box 34, Folder 104)
  - Local 102 Membership meets and Sam Berger resigns Dane Karspacting manager. (Box 34, Folder 105)
  - Local 102 Members meet on Dress orginization Drive, Herbie Sherman, Nat Wallace, D. Karp., Sam Berger, 5/24/52, 1952 (Box 34, Folder 106)
  - Local 102 Journal, 12/46, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 107)
  - Local 102 Conference (Box 34, Folder 108)
  - Picket sign for T.H. injuction, James Knitting Mills and organizer Arthur Jacobson, March 1954 (Box 34, Folder 109)
  - Ratify new agreement at Manhattan Center, 7/30/58, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 110)
  - March of Dimes mgr. Local Louis Nelson shows Umhey petitions of shop collection totaling more than $9,000, 12/16/53, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 111)
  - Elections Rand School Kennith Knitting Mills Coney Island, 3/5/53, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 112)
  - Installation by Zimmerman at Webster Hall, 3/24/53, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 113)
  - Unity Weekend, 6/23 25/50, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 114)
  - Ratify new agreement Roosevelt Hall, 7/27/50, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 115)
  - Conference Hotel Washington Nelson, Lovestone and Jepper, 3/26/50, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 116)
  - Installation at Roosevelt Hall, April 13 (Box 34, Folder 117)
  - French, German, Polish and English (Box 34, Folder 118)
  - Students learn about unions (Box 34, Folder 119)
  - Heller to Austria for ECA, 12/49, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 120)
- Series Local 177
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 121)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 122)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 123)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 124)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 125)
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 126)
- Series Local 481
  - Grasgrow, Kentucky Union and management Conference with Dubinsky, 5/29/58 (Box 34, Folder 127)
- Series Miscellaneous
  - Unknown (Box 34, Folder 128)
- Series AL
  - AL1 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - AL2 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - AL3 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - AL4 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - AL5 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - AL6 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - AL7 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - AL8 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - AL9 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - AL10 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - AL11 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - AL12 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - AL13 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - AL14 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - AL15 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - AL16 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - AL17 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - AL18 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - AL19 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - AL20 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - AL21 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - AL22 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - AL23 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - AL24 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - AL25 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - AL26 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - AL27 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - AL28 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - AL29 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - AL30 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - AL31 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - AL32 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - AL33 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - AL34 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - AL35 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - AL36 (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - AL37 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - AL38 (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - AL39 (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - AL40 (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - AL41 (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - AL42 (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - AL43 (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - AL44 (Box 35, Folder 44)
  - AL45 (Box 35, Folder 45)
  - AL46 (Box 35, Folder 46)
  - AL47 (Box 35, Folder 47)
  - AL48 (Box 35, Folder 48)
  - AL49 (Box 35, Folder 49)
  - AL50 (Box 35, Folder 50)
  - AL51 (Box 35, Folder 51)
  - AL52 (Box 35, Folder 52)
  - AL53 (Box 35, Folder 53)
  - AL54 (Box 35, Folder 54)
  - AL55 (Box 35, Folder 55)
  - AL56 (Box 35, Folder 56)
  - AL57 (Box 35, Folder 57)
  - AL58 (Box 35, Folder 58)
  - AL59 (Box 35, Folder 59)
  - AL60 (Box 35, Folder 60)
  - AL61 (Box 35, Folder 61)
  - AL62 (Box 35, Folder 62)
  - AL63 (Box 35, Folder 63)
  - AL64 (Box 35, Folder 64)
  - AL65 (Box 35, Folder 65)
- Series Labor Stage
  - LS1 (Box 35, Folder 66)
  - LS2 (Box 35, Folder 67)
  - LS3 (Box 35, Folder 68)
  - LS4 (Box 35, Folder 69)
  - LS5 (Box 35, Folder 70)
  - LS6 (Box 35, Folder 71)
  - LS7 (Box 35, Folder 72)
  - LS8 (Box 35, Folder 73)
  - LS9 (Box 35, Folder 74)
  - LS10 (Box 35, Folder 75)
  - LS11 (Box 35, Folder 76)
  - LS12 (Box 35, Folder 77)
  - LS13 (Box 35, Folder 78)
  - LS14 (Box 35, Folder 79)
  - LS15 (Box 35, Folder 80)
  - LS16 (Box 35, Folder 81)
  - LS17 (Box 35, Folder 82)
  - LS18 (Box 35, Folder 83)
  - LS19 (Box 35, Folder 84)
  - LS20 (Box 35, Folder 85)
  - LS21 (Box 35, Folder 86)
  - LS22 (Box 35, Folder 87)
  - LS23 (Box 35, Folder 88)
  - LS24 (Box 35, Folder 89)
  - LS25 (Box 35, Folder 90)
  - LS26 (Box 35, Folder 91)
  - LS27 (Box 35, Folder 92)
  - LS28 (Box 35, Folder 93)
  - LS29 (Box 35, Folder 94)
  - LS30 (Box 35, Folder 95)
  - LS31 (Box 35, Folder 96)
  - LS32 (Box 35, Folder 97)
  - LS33 (Box 35, Folder 98)
  - LS34 (Box 35, Folder 99)
  - LS35 (Box 35, Folder 100)
  - LS36 (Box 35, Folder 101)
  - LS37 (Box 35, Folder 102)
  - LS38 (Box 35, Folder 103)
  - LS39 (Box 35, Folder 104)
  - LS40 (Box 35, Folder 105)
  - LS41 (Box 35, Folder 106)
  - LS42 (Box 35, Folder 107)
  - LS43 (Box 35, Folder 108)
  - LS44 (Box 35, Folder 109)
  - LS45 (Box 35, Folder 110)
  - LS46 (Box 35, Folder 111)
  - LS47 (Box 35, Folder 112)
  - LS48 (Box 35, Folder 113)
  - LS49 (Box 35, Folder 114)
  - LS50 (Box 35, Folder 115)
  - LS51 (Box 35, Folder 116)
  - LS52 (Box 35, Folder 117)
  - LS53 (Box 35, Folder 118)
  - LS54 (Box 35, Folder 119)
  - LS55 (Box 35, Folder 120)
  - LS56 (Box 35, Folder 121)
  - LS57 (Box 35, Folder 122)
  - LS58 (Box 35, Folder 123)
  - LS59 (Box 35, Folder 124)
  - LS60 (Box 35, Folder 125)
  - LS61 (Box 35, Folder 126)
  - LS62 (Box 35, Folder 127)
  - LS63 (Box 35, Folder 128)
  - LS64 (Box 35, Folder 129)
  - LS65 (Box 35, Folder 130)
  - LS66 (Box 35, Folder 131)
  - LS67 (Box 35, Folder 132)
  - LS68 (Box 35, Folder 133)
  - LS69 (Box 35, Folder 134)
  - LS70 (Box 35, Folder 135)
  - LS71 (Box 35, Folder 136)
  - LS72 (Box 35, Folder 137)
  - LS73 (Box 35, Folder 138)
  - LS74 (Box 35, Folder 139)
  - LS75 (Box 35, Folder 140)
  - LS76 (Box 35, Folder 141)
  - LS77 (Box 35, Folder 142)
  - LS78 (Box 35, Folder 143)
  - LS79 (Box 35, Folder 144)
  - LS80 (Box 35, Folder 145)
  - LS81 (Box 35, Folder 146)
  - LS82 (Box 35, Folder 147)
  - LS83 (Box 35, Folder 148)
  - LS84 (Box 35, Folder 149)
  - LS85 (Box 35, Folder 150)
  - LS86 (Box 35, Folder 151)
  - LS87 (Box 35, Folder 152)
  - LS88 (Box 35, Folder 153)
  - LS89 (Box 35, Folder 154)
  - LS90 (Box 35, Folder 155)
  - LS91 (Box 35, Folder 156)
  - LS92 (Box 35, Folder 157)
  - LS93 (Box 35, Folder 158)
  - LS94 (Box 35, Folder 159)
  - LS95 (Box 35, Folder 160)
  - LS96 (Box 35, Folder 161)
  - LS97 (Box 35, Folder 162)
  - LS98 (Box 35, Folder 163)
  - LS99 (Box 35, Folder 164)
  - LS100 (Box 35, Folder 165)
  - LS101 (Box 35, Folder 166)
  - LS102 (Box 35, Folder 167)
  - LS103 (Box 35, Folder 168)
  - LS104 (Box 35, Folder 169)
  - LS105 (Box 35, Folder 170)
  - LS106 (Box 35, Folder 171)
  - LS107 (Box 35, Folder 172)
  - LS108 (Box 35, Folder 173)
  - LS109 (Box 35, Folder 174)
  - LS110 (Box 35, Folder 175)
  - LS111 (Box 35, Folder 176)
  - LS112 (Box 35, Folder 177)
  - LS113 (Box 35, Folder 178)
  - LS114 (Box 35, Folder 179)
  - LS115 (Box 35, Folder 180)
  - LS116 (Box 35, Folder 181)
  - LS117 (Box 35, Folder 182)
  - LS118 (Box 35, Folder 183)
  - LS119 (Box 35, Folder 184)
  - LS120 (Box 35, Folder 185)
  - LS121 (Box 35, Folder 186)
  - LS122 (Box 35, Folder 187)
  - LS123 (Box 35, Folder 188)
  - LS124 (Box 35, Folder 189)
  - LS125 (Box 35, Folder 190)
  - LS126 (Box 35, Folder 191)
  - LS127 (Box 35, Folder 192)
  - LS128 (Box 35, Folder 193)
  - LS129 (Box 35, Folder 194)
  - LS130 (Box 35, Folder 195)
  - LS131 (Box 35, Folder 196)
- Series Labor Stage Portraits
  - LP1 (Box 35, Folder 197)
  - LP2 (Box 35, Folder 198)
  - LP3 (Box 35, Folder 199)
  - LP4 (Box 35, Folder 200)
  - LP5 (Box 35, Folder 201)
  - LP6 (Box 35, Folder 202)
  - LP7 (Box 35, Folder 203)
  - LP8 (Box 35, Folder 204)
  - LP9 (Box 35, Folder 205)
  - LP10 (Box 35, Folder 206)
  - LP11 (Box 35, Folder 207)
  - LP12 (Box 35, Folder 208)
  - LP13 (Box 35, Folder 209)
  - LP14 (Box 35, Folder 210)
  - LP15 (Box 35, Folder 211)
  - LP16 (Box 35, Folder 212)
  - LP17 (Box 35, Folder 213)
  - LP18 (Box 35, Folder 214)
  - LP19 (Box 35, Folder 215)
  - LP20 (Box 35, Folder 216)
  - LP21 (Box 35, Folder 217)
  - LP22 (Box 35, Folder 218)
  - LP23 (Box 35, Folder 219)
  - LP24 (Box 35, Folder 220)
  - LP25 (Box 35, Folder 221)
  - LP26 (Box 35, Folder 222)
  - LP27 (Box 35, Folder 223)
  - LP28 (Box 35, Folder 224)
  - LP29 (Box 35, Folder 225)
  - LP30 (Box 35, Folder 226)
  - LP31 (Box 35, Folder 227)
  - LP32 (Box 35, Folder 228)
  - LP33 (Box 35, Folder 229)
  - LP34 (Box 35, Folder 230)
  - LP35 (Box 35, Folder 231)
  - LP36 (Box 35, Folder 232)
  - LP37 (Box 35, Folder 233)
  - LP38 (Box 35, Folder 234)
  - LP39 (Box 35, Folder 235)
  - LP40 (Box 35, Folder 236)
  - LP41 (Box 35, Folder 237)
  - LP42 (Box 35, Folder 238)
- Series Miscellaneous
  - Local 22 Booklet. October 16-17, 1951. (Box 35, Folder 239)
  - Italian-American Labor Council, Philadelphia (item no.1068), 1963 (Box 35, Folder 240)
  - 1973 (Box 35, Folder 241)